Kite2D Game Framework.
Copyright (C) 2010-2014  Milad Rasaneh <milad_rasaneh2000@yahoo.com>

This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.

------------

Kite2D is a free open source 2-dimensional Game Framework
written in C++ by Milad Rasaneh and published under the GPL license.

------------
تست